DELIVERANCE TIME
With just a simple touch, TB Joshua sets the people free, in the name of Jesus.
Let us hear from this woman.
I am the deceiver.
- What have you done to her?
- I want to destroy her,
- What have you done to the marriage?
- I don't want her to get married.
What have you done to her career?
I took everything - her posh car, her house, her shop and her business.
What have you done to her family?
I destroyed her contact with the family.
How many of you are in this body?
We are 35.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am the great evil spirit - mammon.
What have you made her to do?
I took all her money.
How did you enter her?
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I don't want her to be rich.
Her father made a covenant with me.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Emmanuel
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Nadine and I come from Sweden.
It all started last Sunday, when I got a touch from the the man of God - senior Prophet TB Joshua.
So, I came here today to testify the goodness of God.
I got delivered and I just want to thank Jesus and to thank Prophet TB Joshua for serving Him so faithfully.
Basically, I was six years old, and one day during holidays my cousin and I went to play in the river.
Then I fall into a river - there I met a gorgeous lady.
She was so gorgeous; she was beautiful - I have never seen such beauty.
Even though I was young, I could tell how beautiful she was.
She helped me out of the river by using her hands and putting me out.
At the very big surprise of everybody around the river,
because everybody thought I was dead - nobody was coming out of that pool.
Later that night she came in the dream and gave me like a gold ring.
She became gold, because earlier she was gorgeous black, but that night she became like gold.
She also turned me into gold, the minute I wore that ring;
I become gold and then I was swimming in the river.
Going through the river with her, she was introducing me to different places, fishes and stuff like that.
Then she took like a snake, because she had a snake,
she took a snake's eyes and put it in my eyes like lenses.
From there, if I look at you, you would be like...
You would ask me the questions, especially under the sun, if I was wearing lenses,
because my eyes started changing under the sun.
She gave me powers on my lips, in my eyes, in my breasts and in my private parts.
She gave me influence powers and domination powers as well.
OK, so what were these powers for?
Basically to dominate people, to be attractive as well, and to seduce people.
Any man that would come to me would be possessed,
and his spirit would be sent to the mermaid - to the water.
After that, I grew up obviously and then I became like a...
I saw myself always next to the river or in the water.
Later on, I didn't see to have feet anymore like I have now.
I could have a tail when I was swimming - so, I was growing up in grades;
I was becoming a real mermaid and I was growing up in powers.
OK, you said this happened at the young age of six years.
What started happening in your life from there?
From that time, I had the ability to hear dead people.
If somebody died in the family, I could hear the person asking...
For instance; when one of members of our family died and it was raining, he got cold
and he came to me around midnight saying, "Tell your mum that I need my jacket,
because it is very cold outside", or "I can see people dying".
Everybody dying in the family was always coming to me to say goodbye to me.
So, that spirit that also gave you power in your eyes and you would start seeing the dead people,
and those who were about to die in the family...
... and I could hear people fight sometimes.
I could even see things before they happened, or I could dream about things to happen,
and when they happened, it occurred exactly like in my dreams.
So this was all part of the evil power given to you by the mermaid?
Yes, exactly!
So, what then happened in your life?
Then in my life, basically, I had whatever I wanted to have, even though people didn't want to give it to me.
I would have the possibility to influence them to have what I want.
And when I had troubles, I had the power to dominate and get revenge.
And I didn't have to use much power; I just think about it most of the time
and whatever I think about you; having an accident you would have it.
If I said bad things to you you have It.
And I was basically at some point forbidden to curse a person because it's really it was really happening.
Later on, I used spells because I became more and more curious,
I wanted to know more so I went on the internet,
I ordered books, I entered cults.
At what age later did these powers really start manifesting and attracting people to you
and causing you to have different encounters with people?
At the age of 22, because then I started to understand what frustration, pain disappointment
and disloyal people mean.
I was like, "OK, since people are so disloyal, I'm going to start really using my powers on them."
I was speaking to the mermaid and sometimes she appeared to me in my dream to warn me,
or to ask me if I wanted anything.
She could help me to get powers as well.
I could also initiate people in a way.
OK, so when people would offend you or betray you or annoy you
this is when you would use your powers to attack such a person?
Yes, but for the people that I truly loved; I didn't use they use it on them,
because I understood that they were making just mistakes.
So, I forgave the people that I truly loved.
But the ones that didn't mean anything to me - I will come back at them definitely.
For instance, once a guy lied to me that he was single and then we went out together;
I put his house on fire basically, because he was fighting me with his wife and stuff like that.
After that I felt sorry, because the lady was 'cool' so I put so I just put them back together.
This power to attract and to seduce people - how did you start using that?
I started using that after my first breakup because, I was disappointed.
After that I started using power on men, because the guy that I really loved was gone,
so I didn't feel any love for anybody any more.
So it was basically like I needed to get revenge on everybody that was coming to me.
So, I started using it on them.
If you sleep with me, sorry about what I'm going to say,
in my private part, your sperm was going to be swallowed by the snake that the mermaid gave me.
Because there was a snake in my stomach and his mouth was my private part -
so, any sperm that comes into it goes on the wall.
She actually uses your kids.
Later on you would have problems having babies or if you have babies they would all be imbeciles,
like deformed, disabled kids.
They would be disabled or evil children, or you would not have any kids at all,
because we already took everything from them.
If, for example, you are allowed to have two kids in the natural world;
then we would take them away from you - you would not have any kids anymore.
When you hurt my feelings, I would make you lose everything - your job;
anywhere you would go, there would be no 'openings' for you, no help, no nothing.
People who used to help you would abandon you just because you offended me.
If you offend me, you offend the mermaid because she loved me so much.
She was protecting me.
She was the one fighting for me.
OK, so tell us this spirit of mermaid; did it also begin to give you assignments of who to meet or what to do?
Tell us about how that spirit started using you.
Yeah, she started sending me to do crazy things like drinking;
I wasn't drinking because I grow up as a church kid - I was always in Catholic schools.
For instance, she used to send me to nightclubs.
If I met somebody in the nightclub we would sleep together; no feelings, nothing -
just for her to take whatever luck and wealth or good luck from him.
Sometimes she possessed me; it wasn't me so when you had sex me
you would feel like "wow! this is the best ever" -
but it wasn't me making love to you, it was the mermaid just using my body.
So, that was how she began to send you to go and destroy men,
not for anything other than just to destroy them?
Just to destroy, because I had all the money in the world because I was very wealthy.
I didn't need money from any man, I never went out for prostitution or something like that
because I had all the gold, all the money in the world.
But I needed to bring her servants and spirits and stuff like that.
It was like kind of food in a way, like slaves for her.
How did this situation get worse?
You said you kept looking for more power - what happened next?
Further frustration; for instance once I left my stuff in a girl's garage because I was changing houses,
she asked me to help her with a visa situation.
Then I travelled and when I went there - because it concerned three people - the whole thing changed.
I told her but she didn't believe me.
So, she stole my stuff to make a point and I didn't fought her because I knew that it wasn't her fault.
It was the mermaid making a point because at that time I was getting tired of helping the mermaid,
feeling like, "That's not my portion, it wasn't my portion".
Then from there I started using my powers to get revenge.
I always heard this inner voice telling me "Don't do it, don't do this" -
because there was always a little voice of God calling me not to sin.
But it was more powerful than me, so I went higher and higher and I went to occult to get more powers,
with witches, wizards, pagans, kabbalah and everything - you name it.
I became a witch doctor because I could help and heal people.
I could even advise girls in a love area because men were not really faithful...
Sorry, when you say you became a witch doctor and you could do things for people -
would it be something that would actually benefit them
or is it not something that always had its own cost, its own repercussion?
Definitely it has a cost because whenever you enter a witch doctor's place, you don't go back the same.
When you enter the mermaid, it is helping me to guide you, so I can tell you your whole life -
but it's not me, it's her powers through me she's helping me, she's guiding me,
she's telling me what to say where you are coming from, your history, your background,
and from this she's also stealing your life.
She's basically screening you and seeing what's good and what's not good,
is it necessary to talk to this person,
is this person already destroyed, or she is still worthy.
So you mean that all the help that you claim that you rendered to people is actually destruction in disguise?
Yeah! its destruction in disguise because your problems...
I give you what you want for three, four days, sometimes a month
and then the next month you come back, with another problem,
because I took already your legs so it's only a bunch of problems.
You are going from one problem to another; every time you come there is a new thing.
So, how did it happen that you got yourself into it?
Where you initiated into this practice of witch doctoring, or how did it come about?
It came about because the mermaid was appearing to me.
She was also always asking me physically, because I could see her as anybody else.
She's like, "OK, at this grade, at this stage you should now give me your blood
and I would give you all the powers."
I wasn't really keen for that, but sometimes she put me through situations where I didn't have a choice,
because I went from bad luck, to troubles to losing my fiancée,
to being so sad and nothing was working with my family - nobody...
I didn't have peace anymore because she makes the point when she wants something.
So, I had to accept it and then I went higher in grades.
So, I could even see disease in people without her.
When I became a witch doctor I used to heal people.
I used to read card, draw cards for people.
Sometimes I was telling girls to put three drops of your pee, in the guy's tea
so when he drinks it he is going to be in love with you.
I also use elements like, cards, books, bracelets, rings and everything for myself and for other people.
This bag has few items as well; its just few items that I use, cards and books.
Basically I was a witch - witch doctor.
OK, so you can bring out some of the items and show us what were the ones that you used,
the ones you made for people; and tell how did you go about it.
Basically, it's mixed black magic and white magic, spells and everything.
Nadine
Deliverance Testimony
This one here is the book that I've used like it's an angel cards.
We draw the cards to show people; to guide people with their lives, what's going on,
if things are well and stuff like that it.
This is "archangel raphael", he is the healing "angel".
So, we use those cards...
So, this was how the evil spirits began to teach you how to use these cards to deceive people
into thinking that good things were happening whereas you are taking their good fortune,
destroying their destiny and so on?
Yes, exactly.
And this one here is an a.m.o.r.c. entrance book, if you want to become a rosicrucian.
You use this book and there you have all the papers and prices like insurance fees and stuff like that.
OK, so this is one of the cults you joined in order to get more powers?
Yeah, this is one of the cults to try to get more powers.
Show us what else is in the bag.
There's this belt - it was given to me by a powerful witch.
It's is turning into a snake; is supposed to turn into snake whenever you're in danger,
if somebody wants to attack you,
It is a protection; you attach it around your hips - it's helping you actually.
Yeah, this is the belt.
But it sucks blood actually so you don't see your period, for like six,
four months or two months and stuff like that.
So this is what you were telling us earlier that anything given by a witch or witch doctor,
although it might seem to have a benefit, it actually gives you a greater problem as well,
and that they claim this will give you protection, while at the same time it started affecting
your period and sucking your blood, it's all right?
Exactly.
OK, what other items where you given?
I have this pendulum - it helps you to tell if this spirit is inside.
Normally, all the witches are using it to make sure the spirits are inside the room.
We use it when somebody comes to talk to a dead spirit.
So we can say "Yes", if it goes like this, or "No" if it goes like this, and "Maybe" if it goes like this.
So it helps you to locate the spirit in the room.
OK, so this is one of the items you would use when people would come to you
if they want to speak to the dead or to do spells?
These are some of the items you used to help you in that?
Yes, with a crystal ball as well that I didn't bring here.
So this one here is the healing bracelet and for instance this is tiger's eye here.
You can use it for different things, you can put it in water,
you can you can use this to heal yourself, or to bring good luck to yourself and to bring you like...
For instance, if you reach for something, you put it in the water during the night
and then in the morning you wash with this water.
You take a normal bath and then this water from this tiger's eye;
you rinse yourself with it, you let to dry on your skin, you don't use your towel to dry up.
You let it dry and then wherever you go, it's going to help you.
It also protects against evil eye and evil spirits and bad energy.
OK, so all these bracelets are different forms of protection and like
charms for when you want to get something - this would help you to get that?
- Yeah.
- OK.
I also went to voodoo in Benin Republic, Karen luida (?).
They gave me this ring - it's a voodoo ring.
Whenever you need something you do like this, and then you do this, and then whatever you wish you just ask.
If you feel to be in danger or pressured, if you are you going for a business meeting;
because I'm a businesswoman as well.
It helps you to get whatever you want to get; it gives you power as well.
It's also related to the mermaid in a way - they call it a 'doll'.
There are also the 'serpata'(?) and 'efer'(?)
There are a lot of things charged in it; they put spirits...
I don't know all of them, but they put an energy that will help you and protect you.
It's silver, so it's against vampires and evil eye as well.
So basically this was another charm ring for protection as you were doing this work with the evil spirits?
Yes exactly.
And this one is the blue moonstone ring; you charge it with the moonlight.
The first week of the month there is always moon so you take it and then you charge it under the moon.
You can put it in water or you can rinse it for 30 minutes, and then you put it in the place
where the light is flashing on the ring.
The silver as well is for protection.
This one is supposed to be one of the oldest in Sweden.
Whenever you feel in danger, specifically in a danger of death, one of those things comes out.
It's really protecting you.
As you can see... I almost died in different places, so it is protecting you.
It doesn't come out easily, so it comes out with certain forces.
This necklace is like a charming necklace and protection as well.
Whenever you see it on me you'll feel like "she's beautiful and stuff like that."
You will not see my real face, you will see somebody's else face like the mermaid face.
You will see how beautiful I am, how gorgeous I am, because of this necklace.
It looks like a normal necklace, but it's not a normal necklace.
The one that I'm using for others is one of these because women love witchcraft
for their marriage and their relationship.
So this one; you put the powder in the food.
Whenever the man was cheating or he doesn't want to give you anything,
he will be like a baby after you put it, and he will do everything you ask him to do.
So this one is used to bewitch men.
The man would do everything the woman wants and whenever he goes out he can't 'get hard';
sorry about that.
He can't sleep with another woman, he will be faithful.
It will also make her husband not be able to go out in their marriage,
for people who are suspecting their husband of cheating on them?
Yeah! Even though he goes out with another woman, they will not have sexual encounter.
At that time he will not 'get hard'.
He will feel it, but it will not 'get hard'.
So, she would chase him away.
He would come back to his wife; only with his wife he can have an erection.
Another one is...
These ones as well...
This red one here; you pull like a lemon in the middle of your hand
and then you do like this and then you lick it like that, and then you can call whoever you want,
and you will be given whatever you asked for.
What are the kind of things that you have asked for after doing this, after using this charm?
The woman goes back home.
If she was supposed to have twins we take one of the kids or we take all the kids.
So, that's the price to pay.
She paid maybe - let's say 50$, but she lose more than 50$.
They would asked for like the marriage to come back together, the men be crazy about them, to buy cars,
to build a house, to give them money.
Women want money for business and stuff like that, so they want money from men and the guy to be faithful.
But after using this charm what would they now lose, what would happen to them?
She would have the guy back, but they would lose all the money and everything
because we take everything because the guy would become poor.
She would destroy the guy's life actually without knowing it.
- By using this charm?
- Yeah.
After six months everything is going to go down.
She will leave the guy and everything is going to be bizarre.
It will just help you for a few days, a month, two months, three months, and then you go back to zero,
it will be worse than before.
I initiated twelve people because I was meeting even the devil himself sometimes.
He comes as a monster, sometimes as a gorgeous guy.
So, people really wanted to go fast.
There are people who come and ask you, "Oh I want our girls to love me"
or "I want men to be crazy about me" - even if she's not beautiful.
They will have to close themselves indoor for seven days in the dark.
Then, on the Sunday...
They start on Monday, because it's the day of love.
So, you make any good wish on Monday, and the rest of the day is just sacrifice.
You speak to nobody, your phone is off.
So that is how you initiated many people into this habit of witch... - 12 people?
- Yeah.
- OK.
Tell us what was it that made you begin to get tired of this life
and finally you came here to receive your deliverance?
What got me tired was like - you don't have peace, you don't sleep at night,
she can come and wake you up at any time, and you hear people talking .
Whenever you walk on the street you see people with coffins on their head, and you see people with diseases.
And you can hear people's thoughts, so you become like a crazy person, because you can hear them.
On top of it, she asked me to sacrifice my firstborn.
She wanted me to fall pregnant, and then that baby would have to go for sacrifices.
Then I said no - it was enough!
So, how did you find out about The SCOAN and Prophet TB Joshua?
I found out about Prophet TB Joshua from my hair dresser and from my friend - Patrick.
He introduced me to the church and he asked me to go on SCOAN website.
I went there and the first time I saw senior Prophet's TB Joshua pictures -
it just came straight to my face like this...
I was looking at my computer and I didn't understand how did it happen?
How can it happen that he comes to me like that?
I fell actually on the floor and then when I woke up, I went back - it was different because I could see then.
I tried to watch one of the Church services and I saw fruits in the middle of the church...
I couldn't hear what he was saying - it was like "blah! blah! blah..."
I wondered, what was he saying, was he disabled or something?
And people were clapping and I couldn't hear him.
Then the mermaid appeared and she was so mad, and she said "Turn it off! What are you looking at?"
I said, "I am looking at this man."
She said "No! No! No! Don't watch him."
She said, "Look! He's one of my servants."
I said, "Yeah, he has fruits."
Because when you are worshipping the mermaid, you have to keep fruits with you;
next to your bed, you pray on top of them.
In the morning, you give it away to beggars actually.
When I saw the fruits in the middle of the church, I thought like, "OK, while he is preaching
the mermaid is helping him give the testimonies. Whenever he pick somebody, it is because the mermaid
is telling him to pick the person, because that's what she does.
But you have to keep fruits because she loves fruits.
So you mean that as part of your worshipping of this mermaid spirit,
you always had to have fruits by your bed?
Yes, definitely! In the house, everywhere in the kitchen, in the room.
And when you would give this fruit; you said you would say an incantation over it?
Yeah, you do an incantation on it.
You do like... you can send...
She tells you, "You will have a fever, or ulcer, or something else tomorrow.
Put it on the fruit so that people can eat it."
Whoever eats that food will take that disease, that I was supposed to take.
Sometimes we kill a cow, we fry fish...
We did a party gathering, we cooked and we put all the diseases in the food.
Whoever is going to come to that party will eat my disease, or anybody else's disease.
So instead of what people think you're doing; charity and giving out and being a nice person
you're actually distributing sickness, pain, and problem?
Exactly! We were doing that; like you come to take our problems.
The problems we were supposed to have in 2016; you would take all of them from me.
If I was supposed to have an accident, one of those people would have an accident in my place.
If I was supposed to get an operation, somebody else would have that operation; so I would be fine.
But we had to do it every December each year.
OK, so you you're telling us about how you were watching Emmanuel TV,
and you couldn't hear what the man of God was saying.
What was that?
Was that an audio problem with your television or what?
No problem with my television.
It was the spirit actually who didn't allow me.
She didn't want me to listen to him because she knew I would be disconnected from her.
She didn't want me to watch Emmanuel TV.
I was always arguing with Patrick over the TV and over this Emmanuel TV 24/7.
We couldn't watch another program; only Emmanuel TV all the time - it was too much.
I couldn't stand it because the mermaid was attacking me, which he couldn't see.
It was difficult because basically everything I had, I had because she was blessing me with it.
She was spoiling me.
I didn't want to lose more and more things because of Emmanuel TV.
I didn't want to watch it.
But finally, by the grace of God, you were able to come to The SCOAN and last Sunday
you received your deliverance, when the man of God, prophet TB Joshua prayed for you.
Tell us, what happened when you were in the service before the man of God prayed for you.
When we entered the church I just fell asleep.
I didn't understand; it looked like I had drunk like a sleeping pill, because I was sleeping the whole time,
until I heard like chariots, like big Angel's wings.
They woke me up, I was like, "Oh my God! what is this?"
And I told him, "Look! Who are those angels? What are they doing here?"
They were going around the church, and I was like, "Look they are going around the church".
They were located...
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
It was a huge army - they were surrounding the whole church.
They entered noisily, because it woke me up, and I was like "Oh my God! What is this?"
They went all over the church; they were flying.
I was like, "Look Patrick! Can't you see?"
And he was like, "No. I'm not seeing."
I was like, "How can't he see? They are here."
He couldn't see.
They were checking the church to see if everything was fine, for the prophet to come in.
And one of the angels...
So, before the Prophet came here, they stopped here in the middle and then one of the angels stood in the front
- next to the fruits and said, "OK, you can come in five minutes."
So I told Patrick, "Prophet is coming here in five minutes" and he didn't believe me.
I told him, "Trust me, you will see - he we'll be in five minutes."
Exactly five minutes later the Prophet was here, and it was just weird.
Hallelujah, so this was a sign to you that truly you had come to a place
where you were going to receive your deliverance?
Yes, because I started wondering like, "What's going on?"
Hallelujah!
When the man of God came and prayed for you in the name of Jesus Christ - what happened to you?
We went to the be touched.
While we were walking, I started hearing the voice of the evil saying, "Don't go. What are you doing?
They will put you... People are going to talk about you. You'll be ashamed, Don't go!"
And I was like, "No" Enough is enough. I want to be delivered."
So I was shivering and shaking and I was feeling cold.
When I reached the man of God, he just touched me and then after that I don't remember what happened.
I was just like fighting evil spirit in the dream.
And when I woke up, I was surprised to find myself here, because I didn't know where I was.
I was like, "Where am I? What is this place? Where are we?"
I couldn't find where to go when I came out.
And that's how you realized you have been delivered, is that right?
Yes, that's when I realized I have been delivered.
Lets put our hands together for the Lord Jesus!
So now it's been one week since you received your deliverance,
tell us how are you now after the deliverance and how has your life changed?
After the deliverance something popped out of my lips, because one of the powers as well was on my lips.
It just came out like blood and yellow stuff.
And out of my breast, the thing that men used to suck during sexual intercourse...
Because when they were sucking my breast they felt like it was for pleasure, but they were drinking a substance
- a deadly substance actually.
That deadly substance just came out, like "poof", coming out like from an open tap.
So everything was coming out.
And from my private parts, a tongue that was basically doing this
just came out, so I couldn't suck any sperm anymore.
So you mean you're completely delivered?
I'm completely delivered.
Lets put our hands together for Jesus!
And these dreams and the voices of mermaids and things like that;
are you still being tormented by them or you are sleeping peacefully now?
No, she's talking now far away.
Last night I had a dream where she was like swimming in mud - it wasn't in water.
She was very mad and she was like, "Look what she did to us? Because you left us now we are suffering.
You exposed us.", and stuff like that.
Now, you have left them, you're completely free?
I'm completely free.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands for Jesus Christ.
So lastly, we want to hear what is your word of advice to people watching you all over the world?
My word of advice is: guys seriously, don't play with witchcraft - is not a game, and don't go to witch doctors.
Whenever you set your foot inside a witch doctor's house or office, you don't come back the same,
especially if it's a real witch.
You will lose your soul, you will lose your body and spirit, basically.
Some of them die, so don't go to witches.
Men: be careful of women - always bring her to church, because sometimes,
when we are frustrated we become really evil.
It's good to bring your girl to the church, and it's always good to pray to God and to believe in God,
because we can deliver you from anything.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus one more time!
We rejoice with you for your deliverance and your complete freedom
and we want to encourage you: you are delivered by the Word of God,
so now, continue to make God's Word the standard for your life to maintain this deliverance
and the blessing that follows it, in Jesus name!
Amen!